bangingtunes.com 2006-08-22

# BangingTunes.com Privacy Policy

BangingTunes.com recognizes and respects the privacy of our customers. We understand the importance and sensitivity of providing personal information and ensure your information is safeguarded carefully. BangingTunes.com has created the following privacy policy to explain what personal information is collected and how we use the information provided. 

#### Why does BangingTunes.com collect personal information?

We gather personal information to establish your account, process an online order and inform our customers of new releases, special discounts, offers and contests. Occasionally, we conduct market research including anonymous user analysis, web site administration and development. Any collection of personal information by BangingTunes.com is done to make your shopping experience on our site more convenient and user-friendly. 

#### What personal information does BangingTunes.com collect?

The information we collect is described in the following three categories: transaction information, cookies and marketing. 

#### Transaction Information

When you browse through our site, we collect information on the efficiency and working of our Web site.This information includes the number of times a web page is accessed, the browser used, and paths taken when moving through the Web site.When making a purchase on our site, we will collect your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, and purchase information.This information is kept private and stored in a secure database.We may also use this information to contact you as well as for research and development purposes, marketing and anonymous user analysis. 

#### Cookies

A "cookie" is a small file stored on your computer that enables our server to recognize you.Cookies are used to store web page display settings so that your preference is remembered on your }visit. We also use cookies to allow our server to maintain information about the contents of your shopping cart. You can also choose to accept a cookie that will remember your identity and prevent future authentication requests.You may set the browser on your computer to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the opportunity to accept it or not. 

#### Access log information

Our Web server collects site usage and access data, the logs contain information relating to click-stream data and HTTP protocol elements.We collect this information for completion and support of the current activity, web site administration, research and development. This data will be used by ourselves and our agents. 

#### Marketing

As with most web sites, you have the option to register with BangingTunes.com to receive product and service information, special offers, discounts, enter contests and giveaways, etc.If you choose to receive such information we will ask for your e-mail address.If, at any point you choose not to receive information from BangingTunes.com, you may opt-out of this usage by visiting our unsubscribe page. 

#### How do I update my personal information?

If you have established an account on BangingTunes.com, on the menu select "Edit Details" under the "My Account" option, you will be required to logon with your username and password.If you do not have an account on BangingTunes.com, but have registered to receive e-mail communications, special offers, etc., and would like to edit your information please unsubscribe from our mailing list and re-subscribeWe invite you to contact us if you have any questions regarding our privacy practices. 

#### Dispute Resolution

We invite you to contact us if you have questions about this policy.You may contact us using our contact form.You may call us on 01444 250251, or you may contact us by mail at the following address: 

28 Church Road  
Burgess Hill  
West Sussex  
RH15 9AE  
England  

#### Additional Information

This policy is valid for 1 week from the time that it is loaded.
